A Guide to the Markle Foundation records, Record Group 1-Record Group 3 FA024
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Markle Foundation Administration, 2
  - Markle Foundation Administration - Accession 2, 2; 40.8 Cubic Feet
    - President Lloyd N. Morrisett's Papers, 1927-1992 1965-1992; 1; 24 Cubic Feet 20 boxes
      - Alphabetical Files, 1927-1987 1965-1987; 1
        - United States Council for World Communication Year - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 237)
        - University of California at Davis - Board of Visitors, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 238)
        - University of State of New York - Advisory Board on Regents University Degrees, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 239)
        - "Walden" Project, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 240)
        - Woodrow Wilson Memorial, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 241)
        - Woodrow Wilson Memorial, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 242)
      - Subject Files, 1970-1992; 2
        Together with Subseries 1, this subseries reflect Morrisett's service as an advisor or trustee on boards of corporations, foundations, and institutions of higher learning. Among the most notable are Children's Television Workshop, Oberlin College, RAND Corporation, Systems Development Corporation, Media Commentary Council, Haskins Laboratories, and the American Association for the Advancement of Science.
        The Subject Files subseries includes correspondence, memoranda, records of interviews, minutes of meetings, financial data of organizations and projects, grant proposals, studies, administrative miscellany, photographs, publicity materials, and printed materials.
        - Children's Television Workshop - Benefit Design Group, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 243)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Peter L. Bernstein, 1982-1989 (Box 7, Folder 244)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Audit Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 245)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Charter, By-Laws, Minutes of Organizational Meeting, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 246)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Conflict of Interest Policy, 1977, 1986, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 247)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 248)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 249)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 250)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 251)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - "Enter" Magazine Policy Meeting, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 252)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Executive Committee, 1970-1973, 1975, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982-1983, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 253)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Executive Committee, 1970-1973, 1975, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982-1983, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 254)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Financial Statements, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 255)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Fund for Future Projects, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 256)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Meeting Materials, 1983-1985, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 257)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Meeting Materials, 1983-1985, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 258)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Meeting Materials, 1983-1985, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 259)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Meeting Materials, 1983-1985, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 260)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Memoranda, 1977, 1981, 1983-1984, 1986-1987, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 261)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Memoranda, 1977, 1981, 1983-1984, 1986-1987, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 262)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Memoranda, 1977, 1981, 1983-1984, 1986-1987, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 263)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Memoranda, 1977, 1981, 1983-1984, 1986-1987, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 264)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance Committee - Minutes, 1979-1984 (Box 7, Folder 265)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Finance and Investment Committee Minutes, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 266)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Investment Sub-Committee, 1982-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 267)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Investment Sub-Committee, 1982-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 268)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Investment Sub-Committee, 1982-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 269)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Investment Sub-Committee, 1982-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 270)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Investment Sub-Committee, 1982-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 271)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Investment Sub-Committee, 1982-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 272)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Investment Sub-Committee, 1982-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 273)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Investment Sub-Committee, 1982-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 274)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Investment Sub-Committee, 1982-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 275)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Liability Insurance, 1980, 1987, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 276)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Memoranda, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 277)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Memoranda, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 278)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Memoranda, 1978-1989 (Box 8, Folder 279)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Memoranda, 1978-1989 (Box 8, Folder 280)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Memoranda, 1978-1989 (Box 8, Folder 281)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Memoranda, 1978-1989 (Box 8, Folder 282)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Memoranda, 1978-1989 (Box 8, Folder 283)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Memoranda, 1978-1989 (Box 8, Folder 284)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Minutes, 1983-1991 (Box 8, Folder 285)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Minutes, 1983-1991 (Box 8, Folder 286)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Minutes, 1983-1991 (Box 8, Folder 287)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Minutes, 1983-1991 (Box 8, Folder 288)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Nominating Committee, 1971-1982, 1986-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 289)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Nominating Committee, 1971-1982, 1986-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 290)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Nominating Committee, 1971-1982, 1986-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 291)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Nominating Committee, 1971-1982, 1986-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 292)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Nominating Committee, 1971-1982, 1986-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 293)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Board of Trustees - Special Board Meeting, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 294)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "Breakfast With Max" (Medical Show), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 295)
        - Children's Television Workshop - British Satellite Broadcasting, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 296)
        - Children's Television Workshop - David V. B. Britt, 1980-1991 (Box 8, Folder 297)
        - Children's Television Workshop - David V. B. Britt, 1980-1991 (Box 8, Folder 298)
        - Children's Television Workshop - David V. B. Britt, 1980-1991 (Box 8, Folder 299)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Business Progress and Plan, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 300)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Cable Television, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 301)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Cable Workbook, August 18, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 302)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Compensation of Staff and Trustees, 1973-1989 (Box 8, Folder 303)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Compensation of Staff and Trustees, 1973-1989 (Box 8, Folder 304)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Compensation of Staff and Trustees, 1973-1989 (Box 8, Folder 305)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Compensation Reference Material, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 306)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Joan Ganz Cooney, 1970-1991 (Box 8, Folder 307)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Joan Ganz Cooney, 1970-1991 (Box 8, Folder 308)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Joan Ganz Cooney, 1970-1991 (Box 8, Folder 309)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Joan Ganz Cooney, 1970-1991 (Box 8, Folder 310)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Joan Ganz Cooney, 1970-1991 (Box 8, Folder 311)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Joan Ganz Cooney, 1970-1991 (Box 8, Folder 312)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Corporate Philosophy, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 313)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Corporate Profile, 1984, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 314)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Corporate Review, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 315)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "Creative Classroom" Magazine, 1990, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 316)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Day Care, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 317)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Dental Project, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 318)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Development, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 319)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "Dragons and Dungeons" Game, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 320)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Electric Company Proposal, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 321)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Fiscal Budget, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 322)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Fischer, Francis, Trees and Watts, Inc., November 30, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 323)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "From Time to Time", 1981 (Box 9, Folder 324)
          Series idea.
        - Children's Television Workshop - Fund for Demonstration, Research and Experimentation, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 325)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Fundraising, 1984, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 326)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "Games" Magazine, 1982, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 327)
        - Children's Television Workshop - General Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box 9, Folder 328)
        - Children's Television Workshop - General Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box 9, Folder 329)
        - Children's Television Workshop - General Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box 9, Folder 330)
        - Children's Television Workshop - General Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box 9, Folder 331)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Kenneth J. Gruber, 1988, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 332)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Kenneth J. Gruber, 1988, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 333)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Home Videos, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 334)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Interactive Video Project, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 335)
        - Children's Television Workshop - International, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 336)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Gary E. Krell, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 337)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Legal and Corporate Affairs, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 338)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Gerald S. Lesser, 1980-1990 (Box 9, Folder 339)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Gerald S. Lesser, 1980-1990 (Box 9, Folder 340)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Gerald S. Lesser, 1980-1990 (Box 9, Folder 341)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Gerald S. Lesser, 1980-1990 (Box 9, Folder 342)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Gerald S. Lesser, 1980-1990 (Box 9, Folder 343)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Arthur Lipper, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 344)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Literacy Project, 1988-1989, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 345)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Literacy Project, 1988-1989, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 346)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Literacy Project, 1988-1989, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 347)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Literacy Project, 1988-1989, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 348)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Roger L. Madell, 1985-1991 (Box 9, Folder 349)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Roger L. Madell, 1985-1991 (Box 9, Folder 350)
        - Children's Television Workshop - MacArthur Fund Presentation, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 351)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Magazine Department, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 352)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Mathematics Show "Square One", 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 353)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Mathematics Show "Square One", 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 354)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Mathematics Show "Square One", 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 355)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Mellon Foundation - Children's Television Study, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 356)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Mellon Foundation - Children's Television Study, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 357)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Lloyd N. Morrisett - Advisory Agreement with Mellon Foundation, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 358)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Lloyd N. Morrisett - Biographical Information, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 359)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Lloyd N. Morrisett - Memorandum, March 26, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 360)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Lloyd N. Morrisett - National Advisory Council, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 361)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Lloyd N. Morrisett - Remarks to the Board of Trustees, October 6, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 362)
        - Children's Television Workshop - New Business Opportunities Planning Session, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 363)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "Nickelodeon", 1987 (Box 10, Folder 364)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Personnel and Compensation Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 365)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Planning and Analysis, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 366)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Play Park Project, 1978-1983 (Box 10, Folder 367)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Play Park Project, 1978-1983 (Box 10, Folder 368)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Play Park Project, 1978-1983 (Box 10, Folder 369)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Press Releases, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 370)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Press Releases - Concerning Formation of Children's Television Workshop (CTW), 1968 (Box 10, Folder 371)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Public Relations Goals, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 372)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Publicity Material, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 373)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Publicity Material, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 374)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Publicity Material, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 375)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Publicity Material, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 376)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "Sesame Street", 1987 (Box 10, Folder 377)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "6-9" Literacy Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 378)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "6-9" Literacy Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 379)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Strategic Statement, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 380)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Tenth Anniversary Dinner, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 381)
        - Children's Television Workshop - The New York Times Article Response, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 382)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "3-2-1 Contact", 1979-1982, 1986, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 383)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "3-2-1 Contact", 1979-1982, 1986, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 384)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "3-2-1 Contact" - Draft Proposal, Part I, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 385)
        - Children's Television Workshop - "3-2-1 Contact" - Draft Proposal, Part II, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 386)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1977-1980, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 387)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1977-1980, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 388)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1977-1980, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 389)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1977-1980, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 390)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1977-1980, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 391)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1977-1980, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 392)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1977-1980, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 393)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1977-1980, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 394)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1977-1980, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 395)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1977-1980, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 396)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 397)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 398)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 399)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 400)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 401)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Treasurer's Reports and Memoranda, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 402)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Ventures Corporation, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 403)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Vice President for Administration, 1979-1985 (Box 11, Folder 404)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Vice President for Research, 1984-1989 (Box 11, Folder 405)
        - Children's Television Workshop - Vice President for Research, 1984-1989 (Box 11, Folder 406)
        - Educational Testing Service - Board of Trustees - Background Materials, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 407)
        - Educational Testing Service - Board of Trustees - Forms and Policies, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 408)
        - Educational Testing Service - Board of Trustees - Investment Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 409)
        - Educational Testing Service - Board of Trustees - Investment Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 410)
        - Educational Testing Service - Board of Trustees - Investment Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 411)
        - Educational Testing Service - Board of Trustees - Lloyd Morrisett's "Three Year Report to the President", 1987 (Box 11, Folder 412)
        - Educational Testing Service - Board of Trstees - Memoranda, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 413)
        - Educational Testing Service - Board of Trustees - Nominating Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 414)
        - Educational Testing Service - Board of Trustees - Executive Summary - "Writing to Read", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 415)
        - Educational Testing Service - Chronological File, 1983-1987 (Box 11, Folder 416)
        - Educational Testing Service - Chronological File, 1983-1987 (Box 11, Folder 417)
        - Educational Testing Service - Correspondence File, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 418)
        - Educational Testing Service - Correspondence File, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 419)
        - Educational Testing Service - Correspondence File, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 420)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Executive Committee Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 421)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Executive Committee Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 422)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Executive Committee Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 423)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Executive Committee Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 424)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 425)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 426)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 427)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 428)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 429)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 430)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 431)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 432)
        - Media Commentary Council - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 433)
        - Media Commentary Council - By-Laws, Certificate of Incorporation, Related Correspondence, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 434)
        - Media Commentary Council - By-Laws, Certificate of Incorporation, Related Correspondence, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 435)
        - Media Commentary Council - "Channels" Magazine - Background Materials - Personnel, 1980, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 436)
        - Media Commentary Council - "Channels" Magazine - Background Materials - Publishing Industry, 1979-1980, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 437)
        - Media Commentary Council - "Channels" Magazine - Background Materials - Sample Issues and Ideas, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 438)
        - Media Commentary Council - "Channels" Magazine - Background Materials - Television Criticism, 1976, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 439)
        - Media Commentary Council - "Channels" Magazine - Business Meeting Notes, 1980, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 440)
        - Media Commentary Council - "Channels" Magazine - Consulting Agreements, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 441)
        - Media Commentary Council - "Channels" Magazine - Editorial Advisory Board, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 442)
        - Media Commentary Council - "Channels" Magazine - Editorial Prospectus, June-July 1980, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 443)
        - Media Commentary Council - "Channels" Magazine - Editorial Prospectus, June-July 1980, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 444)
        - Media Commentary Council - "Channels" Magazine - Editorial Prospectus, June-July 1980, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 445)